<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>as.may.moat</id>

  <name>Museum of All Things</name>
  <summary>Explore an infinite 3D museum</summary>

  <developer id="as.may">
    <name translatable="no">Maya Claire</name>
  </developer>

  <description>
    <p>Visit the Museum of All Things, a nearly-infinite virtual museum generated from Wikipedia!</p>
    <p>You can find exhibits on millions of topics, from the Architecture of Liverpool to Zoroastrianism. Search for the topic you want to learn about, or just wander from topic to topic as your curiosity dictates!</p>
    <p>How does it work? The breadth of the museum is made possible by downloading text and images from Wikipedia and Wikimedia Commons. Every exhibit in the museum corresponds to a Wikipedia article. The walls of the exhibit are covered in images and text from the article, and hallways lead out to other exhibits based on the article's links.</p>
    <p>The museum is greatly inspired by educational videos that I watched as a kid, and the liminal spaces produced by early CGI. I want to recapture the promise that the internet can be a place of endless learning and exploration. I hope you enjoy your time exploring the Museum of All Things!</p>
  </description>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>

  <url type="homepage">https://may.as/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/m4ym4y/museum-of-all-things/issues</url>

  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#74c5d8</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#131c5a</color>
  </branding>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://img.itch.zone/aW1hZ2UvMzMzMzMzMC8xOTkwMjQ0NS5wbmc=/original/hNIQFs.png</image>
      <caption>Exhibit of demiregular tiling</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://img.itch.zone/aW1nLzE5OTkyNDAxLnBuZw==/original/V%2Fe9oU.png</image>
      <caption>Exhibit of flowers</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://img.itch.zone/aW1hZ2UvMzMzMzMzMC8xOTkwMjQ0My5wbmc=/original/%2FU1vf5.png</image>
      <caption>Exhibit of Viceroys Portrait Gallery (series in the Chapultepec Castle)</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://img.itch.zone/aW1hZ2UvMzMzMzMzMC8xOTkwMjQ0Mi5wbmc=/original/mFG6kr.png</image>
      <caption>Museum exhibit of Settlers of Catan</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://img.itch.zone/aW1hZ2UvMzMzMzMzMC8xOTkwMjQ0Ni5wbmc=/original/L8S8aS.png</image>
      <caption>Exhibit of various artwork</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="v1.1.0" date="2025-06-10">
      <description>
        <p>This version contains many features built by the community! Probably the largest of these efforts has been multi-language support, developed by @daviirodrig, @zHonys and @akien-mga, as well as the many contributors who helped translating their own languages (thank you to @dekotale, @rschmaelzle, @jasminedevv, @EcSolticia, @wallace-uozato, and @jd-develop !!)</p>
        <p>Currently supported languages as of this release are English, French, German, Spanish, Japanese, Portuguese, and Bengali.</p>
        <p>Version 1.1.0 also includes the following features and bugfixes (listed along with their contributors if applicable):</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Controls can now be rebound in the settings (@TuTiuTe)</li>
          <li>Mouse sensitivity and invert-y settings</li>
          <li>Joypad deadzone settings</li>
          <li>Update to Godot v4.4 (@dsnopek)</li>
          <li>Language can be selected on the main menu and anywhere in the museum lobby</li>
          <li>You can use a virtual keyboard at the search terminal in VR (@dsnopek)</li>
          <li>Add non-latin fonts</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="v1.0.1" date="2025-02-27">
      <description>
        <p>This version fixes some issues that people spotted after release! v1.0.1 has 5 contributors on it now!! Thank you so so much to everyone who's been helping out :)</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Use physical keybinds instead of soft keybinds, to support other keyboard layouts (thank you @akien-mga !)</li>
          <li>Caps the number of wikimedia commons images that can be loaded into an exhibit at 2500</li>
          <li>Fix the clear cache button in the data menu</li>
          <li>Keep exhibits relatively close to the origin-- this fixes a bug that would cause collisions to break after playing for a while</li>
          <li>Footstep player uses polyphonic stream player (thanks @arcaneenergy !)</li>
          <li>Mipmap text labels (not exhibit text plaques yet) and add anisotropic filtering (thanks @stoofin !)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="v1.0.0" date="2025-02-23">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release version</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">as.may.moat.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
</component>
